var questionArray = [{

    question: 'Which NBA player is represented in the NBA logo?',
    choices: ['Jerry West', 'Kobe Bryant', 'Shaq', 'Karl Malone', ],
    answer: 'Jerry West',

},
{
    question: 'What year was Tom Brady drafted?',
    choices: ['1999', '2005',	'1980',	'2000', ],
    answer: '2000',
},
{
    question: 'When did Michael Jordan win his first NBA championship?',
    choices: ['1995', '1991', '1996', '1989', ],
    answer: '1991',
},
{
    question: 'Which US city won the MLS cup in 2015?',
    choices: ['Dallas', 'Seattle', 'New York', 'Portland', ],
    answer: 'Portland',
},
{
    question: 'What age did Tiger woods turn pro?',
    choices: ['16', '25', '20', '21', ],
    answer: '25',
},
{
    question: 'When was the last time Seattle Seahawks wond Superbowl?',
    choices: ['2014',	'1999',	'2017',	'2005',],
    answer: '2014',

},
{
    question: 'Which US state has the most MLB teams?',
    choices: ['New York', 'Texas',	'California', 	'Florida', ],
    answer: 'California' ,
},
{
    question: 'When was the first year of the Womens tennis US Open?',
    choices: ['1887',	'1929',	'1985',	'1954',],
    answer: '1887',
 
},
{
    question: 'Which country held the summer Olympics in 2016?',
    choices:['Russia',	'China',	'Brazil',	'United States',],
    answer: 'Brazil',
},
{
    question: 'How many fouls can you give before you are fouled out in the NBA?',
    choices: ['5','6','4','7'],
    answer: '6',

},
{
    question: 'What is the minimum amount of players on a professional Hockey team?',
    choices:['15','12','25','20'],
    answer: '20',

},
{
    question: 'How many football teams are in the National Footbal League?',
    choices: ['30', '24', '32', '40',],
    answer: '32',

},
{
    question: 'How many teams are in the Womens National Basketball Association?',
    choices:['24','12','20','28'],
    answer: '12',

},
{
    question:'How many points is a touchdown in the NFL?',
    choices:['6','7','8','3'],
    answer: '6'

},
{
    question: 'Which olympic athlete owns the 100 meter world record?',
    choices: ['Justin Gattlin',	'Ben Johnson',	'Usain Bolt',	'Carl Lewis'],
    answer: 'Usain Bolt',

},
{
    question: 'Which Olmpian holds the most medals in indivudal events?',
    choices: ['Michael Jordan',	'Michael Phelps',	'Usain Bolt',	'Larisa Latynina'],
    answer: 'Michael Phelps',
}

];












